{"data":[{"question":"Florida relies heavily on income from fruit crops, and ________.","a":"also California","b":"California too","c":"so does California","d":"California is as well","answer":"3","explain":"+ SO is used to show agreement with positive statements. \n+ SO + Auxiliary + Subject (pronoun).\u00a0\n+ The Auxiliary needs to agree with the verb tense in the original statement.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"},{"question":"She wanted to serve some coffee to her guests, however, ________.","a":"she had not many sugar.","b":"there was not a great amount of the sugar.","c":"she did not have much sugar.","d":"she was lacking in amount of sugar.","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Many\/ a great amount of + countable noun.\n- Much + uncountable noun","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"},{"question":"After the funeral, the residents of the apartment building ________.","a":"sent faithfully flowers to the cemetery","b":"sent to the cemetery faithfully flowers","c":"sent faithfully to the cemetery flowers","d":"sent flowers faithfully to the cemetery","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Adverb modifies Verb (send), adjective modifies noun.\n- Send something to somebody\/somewhere.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"},{"question":"The land and the house that you own are your ________.","a":"property","b":"saving","c":"personal belongings","d":"private area","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Property: the thing or things that someone owns.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"},{"question":"A ________ is an object that help you remember a place you have visited.","a":"memory","b":"souvenir","c":"crime","d":"note","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Souvenir: an object that you buy or keep to remind yourself of a special occasion or a place you have visited.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"},{"question":"If someone commits a ________ in Britain, the police try to catch him.","a":"mistake","b":"divorce","c":"crime","d":"misunderstanding","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Crime: illegal activities in general.\u00a0\n- Commit crime: do something illegal","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"},{"question":"The book contained a lot of ________ about how little petrol the car used.","a":"information","b":"news","c":"fact","d":"examination","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Information and news are uncountable noun.\u00a0\n+ Information: facts or details that tell you something about a situation, person, event (source of information: all sources).\u00a0\n+ News: information about something that has happened recently (source of news: often comes from newspaper, magazine, television, radio...).\u00a0\n- Fact and examination are countable noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"},{"question":"They never expected that ________ find the bicycle.","a":"they are going to","b":"they are will","c":"they would","d":"they shall","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Expect somebody will do sth.\u00a0\n- Simple past tense- would do sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"},{"question":"The car was easy to recognize, ________ it wasn't difficult for the police to catch the thieves.","a":"because","b":"that","c":"so","d":"but","answer":"3","explain":"\n- So: used to say that someone does something because of the reason just stated.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"},{"question":"By the end of next year, they ________ the new stadium.","a":"will finish","b":"finish","c":"will have finished","d":"they are finishing","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The Future Perfect expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future (By the end of next year).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"}]}